xlinesoft.com 2017-07-10

# Xlinesoft privacy policy

### Our privacy policy

Our privacy policy is simple - we do not sell or give your personal information to anyone at any time, ever! 

If You Order.

Our site uses an order form for customers to order our products. We collect contact information (like email addresses), and financial information (like account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to ship orders. Telephone numbers are optional but can be useful for contacting you if there is a problem with your order. Xlinesoft.com does not sell or use your private information (name, address, phone, email address, etc) for any purpose other than to ship you your order or to contact you if there is a problem with your order.   
You will receive a confirmation email immediately after you order. You will later receive a registration code by email with detailed instructions, and possibly a followup thank you email. 

Newsletter.

If you subscribe to our newsletter, your email address will be used only to send you the Xlinesoft Newsletter and not for any other purpose. We do not sell or give email addresses of newsletter subscribers to third parties. If you are subscribed to our newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe@xlinesoft.com](mailto:unsubscribe@xlinesoft.com). 

Web Site.

IP addresses of visitors to our Web site are used to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. IP addresses are also used to compile general demographic information. We will not attempt to identify individual users through their IP addresses. 

We sometimes use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads may be collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Xlinesoft.com itself does not currently use cookies, but our site may use cookies in the future. Cookies may be used to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly as well as to deliver content specific to your interests. 

External Links.

This site contains links to other sites. Xlinesoft.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Contacting the Web Site.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [http://support.xlinesoft.com](http://support.xlinesoft.com/).
